{
    "id": "a0eb742dcca74b82b9b702025110d201",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Work on the new bridge will begin as soon as an official mandate ………………………….",
            "description": "When both clauses refer to the future, we use a future tense in the main clause and a present tense in the subordinate clause.",
            "answers": [
                "is received",
                "will be received"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba8ef91fb57d4abaa96e2798849a3301"
        },
        {
            "question": "Attendance at Sunday chapel is ……………………… longer mandatory for students.",
            "description": "No longer means the same as not any longer.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "no"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0eaa5a5af5744826af26bc10aabfa8a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog’s leg ………………………… in the accident.",
            "description": "We need a passive verb here because the subject is not the doer of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "mangled",
                "was mangled"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a70f571cc794cdfb08c3865522f6641"
        },
        {
            "question": "The principal’s ………………………….. was manifest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unpleasure",
                "displeasure",
                "non-pleasure"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ed89c2b83b74ae5a29acd78f4b5d9e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is ………………………… in danger of extinction?",
            "description": "No article is used with it.",
            "answers": [
                "mankind",
                "the mankind"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8daaaf0c383f4aab8745ea56c953c5ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ship’s ………………………….. being overhauled.",
            "description": "Machinery does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "machineries are",
                "machinery are",
                "machinery is"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6fc3cc3ee9814b3db5c5dbf9e4f09f1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two sisters are mad ………………………… tennis.",
            "description": "When you are mad about something you are infatuated with it.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "498b54634d73450f86f4d7ff7f48d497"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am mad ………………………… him.",
            "description": "When mad means angry it is used with at.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0598b1396d04a55a5cc73d6111b9f62"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you tell us how …………………………….?",
            "description": "Indirect questions have the normal word order. That means the subject goes before the auxiliary verb.",
            "answers": [
                "was the chair made",
                "the chair was made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b71792603d64800b86acb46e5602a1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t make me …………………………….",
            "description": "Make is followed by object + infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b08bee2b2ed14b9383ab11c2852aa647"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked ………………………….",
            "description": "Hastily is the adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "hasty",
                "hastily"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e1731a16525741c4b19a63e89fb830c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has an annoying ………………………… of scratching his head while talking.",
            "description": "A mannerism is a peculiar action or habitual gesture.",
            "answers": [
                "manner",
                "mannerism"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0ed52903f184ed19cfda5c262a55a66"
        }
    ]
}